## MATTHEW HARROP

9638 N Sylvia Ct, Spokane, WA 99208 | (509) 638-8901 | matt\_harrop37@hotmail.com

#### **Skills Summary**

I am a self-directed and very motivated software developer that has been working in IT for the last few years and starting to move my career into the creation of new software. I have experience in backend technologies including Java, C++, Python, and Groovy, as well as front-end frameworks using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript that includes Angular2, React, and Vue. I've worked with frameworks as diverse as PHP's Laravel and .NET and have dabbled in iOS mobile application work as well. I am a quick study and pick up languages and frameworks in stride.

#### Education

Bachelor of Science in Biology (Pre-Medicine), EWU / 2015
Master of Software Engineering, Brandeis University / Currently Attending

#### Experience

## Limelyte Technology Group

Software Engineer / 2020-Present

Implementing a PHP/Laravel API for pulling and pushing background investigation order data to/from a 3<sup>rd</sup> party system, maintaining websites built on Ruby on Rails, PHP/Symfony, Angular, and Vue, and creating a .NET application that connects to a scanner to perform automated drug test analysis.

# Washington Trust Bank

Core Processing Analyst / 2019-2020

Automated daily tasks completed by team using a scheduled Groovy script, resolved incidents within IBM iSeries-hosted banking core system.

# Umpqua Bank

Application Engineer / 2020

Automated interest-rate validation process using a Python script integrated within a FoxTrot automated workflow, prepared business-cases for deploying/upgrading systems, resolved server-side incidents in commercial lending/servicing applications.

Technical Business Systems Analyst / 2017-2019

Implemented new software systems, configured vendor-hosted mortgage servicing systems, troubleshot desktop client issues for those systems.

### Certifications

Google IT Support Professional Certification / 2018